shopstasy.com 2019-04-17

# Shopstasy - All The Fashion Brands You Love, All in One Place

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which _BeOn Media LLC_ collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the _Shopstasy_ website ("Site").

### Personal identification information

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways in connection with activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us.

### Non-personal identification information

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

### Web browser cookies

Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes. User may choose whether to accept cookies by changing the settings on their web browser. If they do so, note that some features may not work as they were intended. We may also use cookies to analyze data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs.

### Sharing your personal information

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others.

### Third party websites

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website's own terms and policies. We may earn a commission when you make a purchase via third party links displayed on our Site.

### Advertising

Ads appearing on our Site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

### Intellectual Property Rights

We do not claim ownership rights in any content posted on our Site by our Users or on third party websites (e.g. Instagram) and displayed on our Site.

### Use of Our Social Media Pages

By posting or submitting content (text, images, photographs or pictures) on our social media pages, you warrant and represent that you own all of the rights to your submission and that you are the copyright owner of such content.

### License

By posting, uploading, providing or submitting user content, you grant _BeOn Media LLC_ a non-exclusive, transferable, sub-licensable, royalty-free, worldwide license to use the user content (in whole or in part) and to incorporate such user content into other works in any format for any and all commercial or non-commercial purposes.

### Changes to this privacy policy

_BeOn Media LLC_ has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect.

### Your acceptance of these terms

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

### Contacting us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, or about the Site, please contact us at [hello@shopstasy.com](mailto:hello@shopstasy.com)

_Last updated on April 07, 2018_
